Hey guys, what's going on?
Josh here, owner and founder of Fast Track USA, the app.
I wanted to talk to you a little bit today about Zia Hussain and his company Zumetrix.
When they took over this project, I was already in the works trying to develop this app for
two years.
Two years trying to get this app going and launched.
They took over and within three weeks my app was launched and it was perfect.
I'm talking about no bugs, no issues, no nothing, it was perfect.
Three weeks, Zumetrix, you guys are amazing.
If you're watching this, I have to tell you, give them a try, give them a chance.
They will solve all your app issues, they will get you going.
Even if you're like me already in the project and not getting anywhere, they'll take over
and they'll get you there to the finish line.
Even if you're starting from ground zero, from nothing, they will take you from the
bottom all the way to the top.
I highly recommend Zia and his team at Zumetrix.
They are amazing, incredible, professional.
They respond quickly, any issues I have, they respond within minutes.
Communication is excellent.
They are top notch team.
I highly recommend them.
They will help you with all your tech and app needs.